Guide to the American Dance Festival Photographic Materials Collection, circa 1930-2008
American Dance Festival Archives
- Company and Biographical, circa 1930-2008
  - Dinizulu and His African Dancers, Drummers and Singers, circa 1983, (prints) (Box 5)
  - Diquis Tiquis, 1993, (prints) (Box 5)
  - Diquis, Tiquis, 1993, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 27)
  - Diquis Tiquis, Publicity, 1993, (prints) (Box 5)
  - Diquis Tiquis, Publicity, undated, (prints) (Box 5)
  - Dlugoszewski, Lucia, undated, (prints) (Box 5)
  - Dorfman, David, 1997, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 27)
  - Dorfman, David, 1997, 1999-2000, 2002, undated, (prints) (Box 5)
  - Dorfman, David, 1999-2000, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 27)
  - Dorfman, David, 2002, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 27)
  - Dorfman, David, Community Workshop, 1997, 2000, (prints) (Box 5)
  - Dorfman, David Dorfman and Dan Froot, 2002, (prints) (Box 5)
  - Dorfman, David Dorfman Dance, 1997, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 27)
  - Dorfman, David Dorfman Dance, 1997, 1999, undated, (prints) (Box 5)
  - Dorfman, David Dorfman Dance, 1999, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 27)
  - Douglas, Dave, 1998, (prints) (Box 5)
  - Douglas, Dave, Publicity, 1998, (35 mm slides) (Box 27)
  - Dowling, Amie and Tom Truss, 1995, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 27)
  - Draper, Paul, 1965, (35 mm slides) (Box 27)
  - Draper, Paul, 1966, (prints) (Box 5)
  - Drzewiecki, Conrad, undated, (prints) (Box 5)
  - Dubois, Groupe Emile Dubois, 1984, (prints) (Box 5)
  - Dudley, Jane Dudley, Sophie Maslow, and William Bales Trio, undated, (prints) (Box 5)
  - Dunbar, Jay, 1998, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 27)
  - Dunham, Katherine, 1986, (35 mm b&w contact sheets) (Box 27)
  - Dunham, Katherine, 1994, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 27)
  - Dunham, Katherine, 1994, undated, (prints) (Box 5)
  - Dunham, Katherine, undated, (8 x 10 b&w negatives) (Box 27)
  - Dunn, Douglas, circa 1977, (prints) (Box 5)
  - Dunn, Douglas, circa 1993, (prints) (Box 5)
  - Dunn, Robert, undated, (prints) (Box 5)
  - Duroure, Compagnie Jean-Francois Duroure, 1989, (prints) (Box 5)
  - Easton, Hilary (YCCP), 1992, (prints) (Box 6)
  - Eglevsky Ballet Company, 1973, (prints) (Box 6)
  - Egyptian Modern Dance Company, 2007, (prints) (Box 6)
  - Eiko and Koma, 1987-1988, undated, (35 mm slides) (Box 27)
  - Eiko and Koma, 1994, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 27)
  - Eiko and Koma, 1996, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 27)
  - Eiko and Koma, 1999-2000, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 27)
  - Eiko and Koma, 2000, (35 mm slides) (Box 27)
  - Eiko and Koma, Performance, 1984–1986, 1989, (prints) (Box 6)
  - Eiko and Koma, Performance, 1994, 1996, 1999-2000, (prints) (Box 6)
  - Eiko and Koma, Publicity, 2000, (prints) (Box 6)
  - Eiko and Koma, Publicity, circa 1984-1996, (prints) (Box 6)
  - Eiko and Koma, Publicity, Photography by Brazil and Leatherdale, circa 1984-1996, (prints) (Box 6)
  - Eiko and Koma, Publicity, Photography by Elbers and Fullard, circa 1984-1996, (prints) (Box 6)
  - Eilber, Janet, 1995, (35 mm slide) (Box 27)
  - El Cubo, circa 1993, (prints) (Box 6)
  - Elkins, Doug (Faculty), 1996, (prints) (Box 6)
  - Elkins, Doug, 1996, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 27)
  - Elson, Steve (YCCP), 1994, (prints) (Box 6)
  - Englund, Richard, undated, (prints) (Box 6)
  - Evans, Bill Evans Dance Company, 1976, (prints) (Box 6)
  - Evans, Bill, 1988, undated, (prints) (Box 6)
  - Evans, Lakey, 1999, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 27)
  - Evans, Letite, undated, (prints) (Box 6)
  - Fagan, Garth Fagan Dance, 1995, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 28)
  - Fagan, Garth Fagan Dance, 1995, 2001, (prints) (Box 6)
  - Fagan, Garth, 2001, (prints) (Box 6)
  - Fagan, Garth, 2001, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 28)
  - Falco, Louis Falco Dance Company, undated, (35 mm b&w contact sheets) (Box 28)
  - Falco, Louis, circa 1968, (prints) (Box 6)
  - Farber, Viola, circa 1960-1998, undated, (prints) (Box 6)
  - Fattoumi-Lamoureux, Compagnie, 1995, (prints) (Box 6)
  - Fattoumi-Lamoureux, Compagnie, 1995, (35 mm slide, 35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 28)
  - Fauzi, Achmad (ICCP), 1994, (prints) (Box 6)
  - Fauzi, Achmad (ICCP), 1994, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 28)
  - Feld, Eliot, undated, (prints) (Box 6)
  - Feldman, Anita Feldman Tap, 1987-1988, (prints) (Box 6)
  - Feldman, Anita Feldman Tap, 1988, (35 mm slides) (Box 28)
  - Fenley, Molissa, 1988, 1997, (prints) (Box 6)
  - Fenley, Molissa, 1997, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 28)
  - Fiadeiro, Joao, 1996, (prints) (Box 6)
  - Fiadeiro, Joao, 1996, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 28)
  - Fine, Vivian, 1964, (35 mm slides, 2 1/4 b&w contact sheet) (Box 28)
  - Fine, Vivian, undated, (prints) (Box 6)
  - First Chamber Dance Quartet, circa 1968, (prints) (Box 6)
  - Flory, Lenka (ICCP), 1996, (prints) (Box 6)
  - Flory, Lenka, 1996-1998, (35 mm, slides, 35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 28)
  - Forces of Nature, 1992, (prints) (Box 6)
  - Forostyany, Valentin (ICR), 1998, (prints) (Box 6)
  - Franklin, Eric, 1996, (prints) (Box 6)
  - Franklin, Eric, 1996, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 28)
  - Free Ballet, 1993, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 28)
  - Free Ballet, 1993, (prints) (Box 6)
  - Friday, William and Ida, undated, (prints) (Box 6)
  - From the Horse's Mouth, 2001, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 28)
  - From the Horses Mouth, 2001, (prints) (Box 6)
  - Gades, Antonio, circa 1966, (prints) (Box 7)
  - Gades, Antonio, circa 1966, (prints) (Box 7)
  - Gallman's Newark Dance Theatre, circa 1989, (prints) (Box 7)
  - Gameche, Abelardo (ICCP), 1989, (8 x 10 b&w negatives) (Box 28)
  - Gameche, Abelardo, 1989, (prints) (Box 7)
  - Gamson, Annabelle, 1976, (prints) (Box 7)
  - Garcia, Roberto, undated, (prints) (Box 7)
  - Gelewski, Rolf, undated, (prints) (Box 7)
  - Gilbert, Gail, 2000, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 28)
  - Giles, Tom, undated, (prints) (Box 7)
  - Gillespie, Dizzy, 1977, (prints) (Box 7)
  - Glover, Savion, circa 1992, (prints) (Box 7)
  - Goldhuber and Latsky, 1997, (prints) (Box 7)
  - Goldhuber and Latsky, 1997, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 28)
  - Gordon, David Gordon/Pick Up Company, 1984-1985, (prints) (Box 7)
  - Goslar, Lotte, 1968, (prints) (Box 7)
  - Gotheiner, Zvi (YCC), 1992, (prints) (Box 7)
  - Graham, Martha, 1957, undated, (prints) (Box OS1)
  - Graham, Martha, 1957, 1964, undated, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w copy slides, 35 mm b&w contact sheets, 2 1/4 b&w contact sheet, 8 x 10 b&w negatives, 5 x 7 b&w negative, 4 x 5 b&w negative) (Box 28)
  - Graham, Martha, Headshots, undated, (prints) (Box 7)
  - Graham, Martha, Performance, undated, (prints) (Box 7)
  - Graham, Martha, Publicity, 2000, (prints) (Box 7)
  - Graham, Martha, Teaching, 1957-1958, (prints) (Box 7)
  - Graham, Martha Graham Dance Company, 1990, undated, (35 mm slides) (Box 28)
  - Graham, Martha Graham Dance Company, Performance, 1972, (prints) (Box 7)
  - Graham, Martha Graham Dance Company, Performance, 1990, (prints) (Box 7)
  - Graham, Martha Graham Dance Company, Publicity, 1962, (prints) (Box 7)
  - Graham, Martha Graham Dance Company, Publicity, 1981, (prints) (Box 7)
  - Graham, Martha Graham Dance Company, Publicity, 2000, (35 mm slides) (Box 28)
  - Graham, Martha Graham Dance Company, Publicity, circa 1967, (prints) (Box 7)
  - Graham, Martha Graham Dance Company, undated, (prints) (Box 7)
  - Graham, Martha Graham Dance Company, undated, (prints) (Box OS1)
  - Graham, Martha Graham Dance Group, 1935-1941, (prints) (Box 7)
  - Gray, Dianne, 1980, (35 mm slides) (Box 28)
  - Greco, Jose, 1970, (prints) (Box 7)
  - Greco, Jose Greco II and Company, 1992, (prints) (Box 7)
  - Grenke, David, 1997, (prints) (Box 7)
  - Grenke, Davis, 1997-1998, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 28)
  - Griffin, Johnny, undated, (prints) (Box 7)
  - Gross, Steve, 1995, (prints) (Box 7)
  - Gross, Steve, 1995, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 28)
  - Groupe de Recherche Choreographique de l'Opera de Paris, 1985, (prints) (Box 7)
  - Grubel, Barbara, 1996, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 28)
  - Grubel, Barbara, 1996, (prints) (Box 7)
  - Guandong, undated, (35 mm slides, 8 x 10 b&w negatives) (Box 28)
  - Guandong Modern Dance Company, 1991, (prints) (Box 7)
  - Guthrie, Nora and Ted Rotante, 1973, (prints) (Box 7)
  - Gutierrez, Miguel, 2001, (prints) (Box 7)
  - Gutierrez, Miguel, 2001, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 28)
  - Haim, Mark, 1995-1997, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 28)
  - Haim, Mark, 1997-1998, 2000, 2002, (prints) (Box 8)
  - Haim, Mark, 1999-2000, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 28)
  - Hall, Arthur, circa 1978, (prints) (Box 8)
  - Hall, Arthur Hall Afro-American Dance Ensemble, circa 1978, (prints) (Box 8)
  - Hall, Arthur, 1979, (35 mm slides) (Box 28)
  - Hall, Joel, circa 1988, (prints) (Box 8)
  - Hall, Joel Hall and Dancers, circa 1988, (prints) (Box 8)
  - Hall, Joel Hall Dancers, 1988, (35 mm slides, 8 x 10 negatives) (Box 28)
  - Halprin, Anna, 1976, (prints) (Box 8)
  - Halprin, Anna, 1986, (prints) (Box 8)
  - Halprin, Anna, 1996, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 28)
  - Halprin, Anna, 1996-1997, (prints) (Box 8)
  - Halprin, Anna, 1997, (prints) (Box OS1)
  - Halprin, Anna, 1997, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 28)
  - Hamilton, Ishvani, circa 1956, (prints) (Box 8)
  - Han Young, Suk, 1986, (prints) (Box 8)
  - Han Young-Suk, 1986, (35 mm slide) (Box 28)
  - Hanayagi, Suzuki, circa 1961, (prints) (Box 8)
  - Harris, Rennie Harris PureMovement, 2001, (prints) (Box 8)
  - Harris, Rennie Harris Puremovement, 2001, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 28)
  - HARRY, 1989, (prints) (Box 8)
  - Hawkins, Erick, 1940, 1962, 1964, 1980, 1988, undated, (prints) (Box 8)
  - Hawkins, Erick, 1940, 1962, undated, (35 mm slides, 8 x 10 b&w negatives, 5 x 7 b&w negative) (Box 28)
  - Hawkins, Erick Hawkins Dance Company, 1964, 1973, undated, (prints) (Box 8)
  - Hawkins, Erick Hawkins Dance Company, 1980, (8 x 10 b&w negative) (Box 28)
  - Hawkins, Erick Hawkins Dance Company, 1980, (prints) (Box 8)
  - Hawkins, Erick Hawkins Dance Company, 1988, (prints) (Box 8)
  - Hawkins, Erick Hawkins Dance Company, 1988, undated, (35 mm slides, 8 x 10 b&w negative) (Box 28)
  - Hawkins, Erick Hawkins Dance Company, 1989-1994, (prints) (Box 8)
  - Hawkins, Erick Hawkins Dance Company, 1994, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 28)
  - Hawkins, Erick Hawkins Dance Company, 1996, (prints) (Box 8)
  - Hawkins, Erick Hawkins Dance Company, 1996, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 28)
  - Hayashi, Michiko, 1985, (prints) (Box 8)
  - Hayes, Deborah, undated, (5 x 7 b&w negative) (Box 28)
  - Hemphill, Ellen, 1995, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 28)
  - Hersch, Fred, 1997, (prints) (Box 8)
  - Hersch, Fred, 1997, (35 mm slides) (Box 28)
  - Herve, Myriam (ICCP), 1996-1997, (prints) (Box 8)
  - Herve-Gil, Myriam, 1996-1997, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 28)
  - Heustess, David, 1985, (prints) (Box 8)
  - Hill, Martha, 1978, (35 mm slides) (Box 28)
  - Hill, Martha, Headshots, circa 1935, (prints) (Box 8)
  - Hill, Martha, Other, circa 1940-1969, (prints) (Box 8)
  - Hill, Martha, Performance, circa 1937, (prints) (Box 8)
  - Ho, Hsiao-Mei (ICCP), 1995, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 28)
  - Ho, Hsio-Mei, 1995, (prints) (Box 8)
  - Hodes, Linda, 1992, (prints) (Box 8)
  - Holm, Hanya Holm Group, circa 1930, (prints) (Box 8)
  - Holm, Hanya, 1936, (8 x 10 b&w negative, 5 x 7 b&w negative) (Box 28)
  - Holm, Hanya, 1984, (prints) (Box 8)
  - Holm, Hanya, 1984, (35 mm b&w contact sheet) (Box 28)
  - Holm, Hanya, Headshots, Performance, circa 1930, 1980, (prints) (Box 8)
  - Holm, Hanya, undated, (prints) (Box OS1)
  - Horst, Louis, circa 1935, 1960-1961, (prints) (Box 8)
  - Horton, Lester, 1984, (5 x 7 b&w negatives, 4 x 5 b&w negative) (Box 28)
  - Houlihan, Gerri, 1994, 1996-1998, 2002, (prints) (Box 8)
  - Houlihan, Gerri, 1996-1997, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 28)
  - Houseman, John, undated, (prints) (Box 8)
  - Hoving, Lavinia, 1972, (prints) (Box 9)
  - Hoving, Lucas, 1949, 1963-1966, undated, (prints) (Box 9)
  - Hoving, Lucas, 1954, (prints) (Box 9)
  - Hoving, Lucas, 1965, 1978, undated, (35 mm slides, 2 1/4 b&w contact sheets, 8 x 10 b&w negatives) (Box 28)
  - Hoving, Lucas, 1978, 1987-1989, (prints) (Box 9)
  - Hoving, Lucas, ILP Residency at Guandong, China, 1989, (prints) (Box 9)
  - Hoving, Lucas, undated, (prints) (Box OS1)
  - Hoving, Lucas Hoving Dance Company, 1965, (prints) (Box 9)
  - Hoving, Lucas Hoving Dance Company, 1971, (prints) (Box 9)
  - Hoving, Lucas Hoving Dance Company, undated (4 folders), (prints) (Box 9)
  - Howard, Theresa, 2000, (prints) (Box 9)
  - Huang, Al, 1966, 1969, (prints) (Box 9)
  - Hubbard Street Dance Chicago, 1993, (prints) (Box 9)
  - Hubbard Street Dance Chicago, 1993, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 28)
  - Humphrey, Doris, 1936, undated, (prints) (Box 9)
  - Humphrey, Doris, 1953, (prints) (Box 9)
  - Humphrey, Doris, undated, (prints) (Box OS1)
  - Humphrey, Doris Humphrey, Charles Weidman and Company, undated, (prints) (Box 9)
  - Humphrey, Doris, With My Red Fires, 1936, (8 x 10 b&w negatives) (Box 28)
  - Inner City Repertory Dance Company, 1973, (prints) (Box 9)
  - Ito, Sachiyo, 1976, (prints) (Box 9)
  - Jackson, Lynn, 1995-1996, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 29)
  - Jackson, Lynn, 1996, (prints) (Box 9)
  - Jamison, Judith, 1976, (prints) (Box 9)
  - Jasperse, John, 2000, (prints) (Box 9)
  - Jasperse, John, 2000, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 29)
  - Jasperse, John (ICCP), Dry, 2002, (prints) (Box 9)
  - Jasperse, John Jasperse Company, 1999, (35 mm slides, 35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 29)
  - Jasperse, John Jasperse Company, 1999, 2001, (prints) (Box 9)
  - Jasperse, John Jasperse Company, 2001, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 29)
  - Jazz Dance: The Danny Buraczeski Dance Company, 1982, (prints) (Box 9)
  - Jazz Professors, undated, (prints) (Box 9)
  - Johnson, Bernard, undated, (prints) (Box 9)
  - Johnson, Hazel, 1964, (35 mm slides) (Box 29)
  - Johnson, Raymond, undated, (prints) (Box 9)
  - Jones, Betty, 1965, undated, (35 mm slides, 2 1/4 b&w contact sheets) (Box 29)
  - Jones, Betty, 1979, (35 mm slides) (Box 29)
  - Jones, Betty, 1993, undated, (35 mm slide, 35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 29)
  - Jones, Betty, 1996, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 29)
  - Jones, Betty, Headshots, 1998-1999, undated, (prints) (Box 9)
  - Jones, Betty, Performance, 1958, 1962, 1986, undated, (prints) (Box 9)
  - Jones, Betty, Teaching, 1958, 1982, 1986, 1993, 1999, undated, (prints) (Box 9)
  - Jones, Bill T., 1994-1995, undated, (prints) (Box 9)
  - Jones, Bill T., 1997, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 29)
  - Jones, Bill T., 1997, 1999, (prints) (Box 9)
  - Jones, Bill T. Jones/Arnie Zane Dance Company, 1989, 1991, (prints) (Box 9)
  - Jones, Bill T. Jones/Arnie Zane Dance Company, 1989, undated, (prints) (Box OS1)
  - Jones, Bill T. Jones/Arnie Zane Dance Company, 1994, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 29)
  - Jones, Bill T. Jones/Arnie Zane Dance Company, 1995, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 29)
  - Jones, Bill T. Jones/Arnie Zane Dance Company, 1995, 1997, (prints) (Box 9)
  - Jones, Bill T. Jones/Arnie Zane Dance Company, 1997, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 29)
  - Jones, Bill T. Jones/Arnie Zane Dance Company, 1997, 1999, (prints) (Box 9)
  - Jones, Bill T. Jones/Arnie Zane Dance Company, 1999, (prints) (Box 9)
  - Jones, Bill T. Jones/Arnie Zane Dance Company, 1999, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 29)
  - Jones, Bill T. Jones/Arnie Zane Dance Company, Publicity, undated, (prints) (Box 9)
  - Kala Mandapa Institute of the Nepalese Performing Arts, undated, (prints) (Box 10)
  - Kato, Miyako Kato and Dancers, 1982, (prints) (Box 10)
  - Kaye, Pooh, 1984, (35 mm b&w contact sheets) (Box 29)
  - Kaye, Pooh, 1985, undated, (prints) (Box 10)
  - Kaye, Pooh Kaye/Eccentric Motions, circa 1986, (prints) (Box 10)
  - Keen, Elizabeth Keen Dance Company, circa 1975, (prints) (Box 10)
  - Kela, Reijo, 1987-1989, (prints) (Box 10)
  - Kela, Reijo, 1991, (35 mm slides) (Box 29)
  - Kela, Reijo, undated, (8 x 10 b&w negatives, 4 x 5 b&w negatives) (Box 29)
  - Kelly, Paula, circa 1965, (35 mm slides) (Box 29)
  - Kim, Sam-Jin (ICW), 1993, (prints) (Box 10)
  - Kim, Sam-Jin (ICW), 1993, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 29)
  - Kimoto, Kumiko, 1995, (prints) (Box 10)
  - Kimoto, Kumiko, undated, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 29)
  - Kinney, Sharon, 1979, (35 mm slides) (Box 29)
  - Kinney, Sharon, 1980, 1985, (35 mm slides) (Box 29)
  - Kinney, Sharon, 1986, undated, (prints) (Box 10)
  - Kisselgoff, Anna, 1995, (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 29)
  - Knaack, Donald, 2000, (35 mm slides) (Box 29)
  - Koner, Pauline Koner Dance Consort, 1975, 1978, undated, (prints) (Box 10)
  - Koner, Pauline, 1978, undated, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w contact sheets) (Box 29)
  - Koner, Pauline, 1998, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 29)
  - Koner, Pauline, circa 1950, (prints) (Box 10)
  - Koplowitz, Steven Koplowitz and Company, 1989, (prints) (Box 10)
  - Kovich, Robert (YCC), 1986, (prints) (Box 10)
  - Kozadaev, Sergei (ICW), 1990, (prints) (Box 10)
  - Kulygin, Alexander, 1998, (prints) (Box 10)
  - Kusumo, Sardona (ICCP),1998, (prints) (Box 10)
  - La Compagnie Ris et Danceries, 1989, (prints) (Box 10)
  - La Meri, 1961, (prints) (Box 10)
  - La P'tite Cie, 1989, (prints) (Box 15)
  - La P'tite Cie, undated, (8 x 10 b&w negative) (Box 31)
  - Lang, Pearl, 1964, undated, (prints) (Box 10)
  - Lang, Pearl, 1964-1965, (35 mm slides, 2 1/4 b&w contact sheet) (Box 29)
  - Lang, Pearl, 1978, (prints) (Box OS1)
  - Langland, Paul, undated, (prints) (Box 10)
  - Latimer, Lenore, 1966, undated, (prints) (Box 10)
  - Latsky, Heidi, 1996-1997, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 29)
  - Latsky, Heidi, 1997, (prints) (Box 10)
  - Ledezma, Jose, 1985, (prints) (Box 10)
  - Leichter, Nicholas, 1998, 2000, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets, 35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 29)
  - Leichter, Nicholas, 2000, (prints) (Box 10)
  - Lemon, Ralph Lemon Company, 1994, undated, (prints) (Box 10)
  - Lemon, Ralph Lemon Company, undated, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 29)
  - Lepkoff, Daniel, 1995-1996, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 29)
  - Lepkoff, Danny, 1996, (prints) (Box 10)
  - L'Equisse, Compagnie de dance, 1987, (35 mm slides) (Box 29)
  - Lerman, Liz Lerman and the Dance Exchange, 1981-1992, (prints) (Box 10)
  - Lerman, Liz, 1986-1992, (prints) (Box 10)
  - Levi, Richard, 1983, (prints) (Box 10)
  - Levy, Ofra (ICC), 1995, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 29)
  - Levy, Ofra, 1995, (prints) (Box 10)
  - Lewis, Daniel, undated, (prints) (Box 10)
  - Lewitsky, Bella, 1983, 1994, (prints) (Box 10)
  - Lewitsky, Bella, 1984, (8 x 10 b&w negative, 4 x 5 b&w negative) (Box 29)
  - Lewitsky, Bella, 1994, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 29)
  - Lewitsky, Bella Lewitsky Dance Company, 1972-1979, 1986-1987, (prints) (Box 10)
  - Lewitsky, Bella Lewitsky Dance Company, circa 1970, (prints) (Box 10)
  - Lieberman, Bruce, 1980, (35 mm slide) (Box 29)
  - Limon, Jose, 1951, undated, (prints) (Box 10)
  - Limon, Jose, 1965, undated, (2 1/4 b&w negatives and contact sheets, 35 mm b&w contact sheets, 35 mm copy transparencies, 8 x 10 b&w negative, 4 x 5 b&w negative) (Box 29)
  - Limon, Jose, Performing, 1934, 1954, undated, (prints) (Box 10)
  - Limon, Jose, Performing, circa 1958-1960, (prints) (Box 10)
  - Limon, Jose, Performing, circa 1964, 1968, (prints) (Box 10)
  - Limon, Jose, Performing, Rehearsing, circa 1950-1960, (prints) (Box 10)
  - Limon, Jose, Teaching, 1950, 1953, 1961, 1966, undated, (prints) (Box 10)
  - Limon, Jose Limon Dance Company, 1964, undated, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w contact sheets, 2 1/4 b&w contact sheets, 8 x 10 b&w negative) (Box 29)
  - Limon, Jose Limon Dance Company, 2000, (35 mm slides, 35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 29)
  - Limon, Jose Limon Dance Company, Moor’s Pavane, undated, (prints) (Box 11)
  - Limon, Jose Limon Dance Company, Nightspell, Emperor Jones, 1972, undated, (prints) (Box 11)
  - Limon, Jose Limon Dance Company, Performances, Looking at Dance, 1997, 2000, (prints) (Box 11)
  - Limon, Jose Limon Dance Company, Performance, undated (3 Folders), (prints) (Box 11)
  - Limon, Jose Limon Dance Company, Performances, 1987, (prints) (Box 11)
  - Limon, Jose Limon Dance Company, Photographer: Fannie H. Melcer, undated, (prints) (Box 11)
  - Limon, Jose Limon Dance Company, Photographer: Martha Swope, undated, (prints) (Box 11)
  - Limon, Jose Limon Dance Company, Photographer: Philip Biscuti, 1964, 1968, (prints) (Box 11)
  - Limon, Jose Limon Dance Company, Photographers: Patricia Jean Moore, Matthew Wysocki, undated (2 Folders), (prints) (Box 11)
  - Limon, Jose Limon Dance Company, Publicity, 2000, (prints) (Box 11)
  - Limon, Jose Limon Dance Company, Publicity, undated, (prints) (Box 11)
  - Limon, Jose Limon Dance Company, The Traitor, 1954, 1965, undated (3 Folders), (prints) (Box 11)
  - Limon, Jose Limon Dance Company, There Is a Time, undated, (prints) (Box 11)
  - Limon, Jose Limon Dance Company, Touring, circa 1950, (prints) (Box 11)
  - Limon, Jose Limon Dance Company, undated, (prints) (Box OS1)
  - Limon, Jose Limon Dance Foundation, 1997, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 29)
  - Lohoeffer, Evelyn, 1964-1965, (35 mm slides, 2 1/4 b&w contact sheet) (Box 29)
  - Lohoeffer, Evelyn, undated, (prints) (Box 11)
  - London Contemporary Dance Theatre, 1984, (35 mm slide) (Box 29)
  - London Contemporary Dance Theatre, Photographer: Crickmay, 1975, 1977, 1979, undated, (prints) (Box 11)
  - London Contemporary Dance Theatre, Photographers: Buckland, Anderson, 1983, 1984, undated, (prints) (Box 11)
  - Lopez, Hercilia (ICR), 1990, (35 mm slide) (Box 29)
  - Lopez, Hercilia, 1989, 1990, 1993, (prints) (Box 11)
  - Lopez-Barrantes, Rafael, 1993, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 29)
  - Lopez-Barrantes, Rafael, 1996, (prints) (Box 11)
  - Losdenmedium, 1992, (prints) (Box 11)
  - Louis, Murray, Publicity, circa 1972, undated, (prints) (Box 11)
  - Luahine, Iolani, 1975, (prints) (Box 12)
  - Lubovitch, Lar, undated, (prints) (Box 12)
  - Lubovitch, Lar Lubovitch Dance Company, circa 1983, (prints) (Box 12)
  - Lubovitch, Lar Lubovitch Dance Company, circa 1989, (prints) (Box 12)
  - Lubovitch, Lar Lubovitch Dance Company, undated, (35 mm slides) (Box 29)
  - Ludin, Fritz, circa 1967, (prints) (Box 12)
  - Lyon Opera Ballet, 1997, (prints) (Box 12)
  - Lyon Opera Ballet, 1997, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 29)
  - Mabou Mines, 1974, (prints) (Box 12)
  - MacDougal, Lorn, 1988, (prints) (Box 12)
  - Magee, Keven, False Alarm Theatre, undated, (prints) (Box 12)
  - Maggio, Robert (YCC composer), 1994, (prints) (Box 12)
  - Maharaj, Birju Maharaj and Dancers, 1991, undated, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30)